

Roman Riianov

Front-end developer

Experience



Yandex.Practicum

Jan 2022 — Nov 2022

Front-end developer (student)

During studying, I've implemented the following projects:

- Search film service, client and server parts are been made:
 - · displaying film list by keyword
 - · saving chosen films in the Favourite page on back-end side
 - · saving search filters and page state on the browser side
 - mounting on page different components for authorized/unauthorized users

Stack: JS, HTML, CSS, React.js, MongoDB, Express.js, Joi, Celebrate, Formik https://roman.diploma.nomoredomains.icu

· Mesto

Simplified Instagram analog, implemented adding and deleting images, registration and authorization via JWT cookie, changing user information, popup windows with dimming, and forms validation.

Stack: JS, HTML, CSS, React.js, ESLint, Webpack, Git https://romanriyanov.github.io/react-mesto-auth

· Landing 'Traveling in Russia'

The one-page site that supports adaptive change of display in conformity with media queries.

Stack: JS, HTML, CSS, flex-layout, grid-layout, responsive design https://romanriyanov.github.io/russian-travel-look/index.html

All projects passed code review and been accepted only if according to the technical task



Sep 2016 — Jul 2022

Engineer

- Carried out maintenance of the life cycle of aviation engines: producing, technical maintenance, searching and fixing malfunctions, repair and decommissioning.
- Represents interests of the production factory at operators: duties included communication with domestic and foreign customers, resolution of disputes, guarantee presentations, and claim work.
- Traveled on business trips by tech brigade chief. Took part in the commissioning of experimental technic. Have gratitude and encouragement.

L +7 985 870 84 77

riyanovrv@gmail.com

https://github.com/RomanRiyanov

https://facebook.com/romanriianov

Education

USATU

Engineer

Technical maintenance of aircraft and aircraft engines

2009 - 2015

Skills



Language

English

Russian

German

Hobby

Unusual movies

Surfing

About me

Successfully worked as an aeronautical engineer, but exhausted all growth opportunities. Changed qualification to developer: front-end attracts me to wide spectrum of usage and tangible results of my work.

During my time hitchhiked from Saint - Petersburg to Barcelona and from Vladivostok to Tomsk.